It might be a little scary... if I see it alone at night.
I see, but let's take a look.
It's so realistic.
I'd like to see it.
The Godfather.
The Godfather?
The main character's father... the Godfather...
He has a unique way of speaking.
Like a motorcycle.
He talks like that.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's amazing.
I heard you rebuilt Marugame Seika and others.
Here and there.
What?
You're a math genius!
That's amazing.
I really hate math too, even though he's like this.
I've always wanted to incorporate that way of thinking into something.
It's important, isn't it?
The thought, the atmosphere...
I love it, but it's also about momentum.
But I don't mean that in a different way.
I think it's important when you have to explain to someone that this is the reason why you do what you do.
There are times when you have to explain to the other person that this is the reason why something is the way it is.
I think it's very important to think mathematically in those situations.
There is a formula and an answer.
So, let's give it a try.
I think that's what Michiyoshi is saying.
Big brother!
Michiyoshi next door.
He's my classmate's brother.
He lends me records and stuff.
How kind!
He also lent me some pants.
Pants?
What's a bon-bon?
You don't have any right now?
They don't call them dongs.
They don't say that anymore?
Thick pants?
The ones with the "tutu" at the bottom.
I think they're going to come out with a normal type of school uniform.
About three times wider.
That's the bon-ton.
Tucked here.
Not a tuck, a tuck.
Tuck.
It's like a thin white vinyl belt.
Tuck it in like this.
Did you do that?
No, no, no. What do you mean?
I'm just a meta-human.
I've done this before.
You and your brother, you were doing it, weren't you?
No, I didn't.
You sound like a naughty boy.
I'm a Westerner.
A Westerner.
I think he was a gamer or something.
Chimer's old?
Chima was in 1990.
You don't know about Color Gang, do you?
I learned about the Color Gang from an anime called Durarara.
It's in there too.
It's set in Ikebukuro.
Ikebukuro West Gate Park.
It became famous.
You can tell the gang of delinquents by their colors.
It's like a mask.
The yellow group and the black group
Ikebukuro West Gate Park was like that.
They all put on a color and said, "We're on the same team.
And then they'd win or something.
It's so bad.
With metal bats and stuff.
Scary.
That's why they were called "teamers" back then.
That's why they called you a teamer?
When I was in Odadera, I was more of a delinquent.
We were called "toppari".
A man's a thug when he's a thug.
Tsuppari has become more sophisticated.
It's become more Shibuya-like.
It's not traditional.
They wear something like American field hockey uniforms.
And then the coolest look was the teamer.
It was fashionable.
There are no guys like Cheemer?
No, there aren't.
What are these juvenile delinquents doing and where?
You don't have an army like that, do you?
I don't know.
But Machida, for example...
You okay?
What's with the little bike?
With a gen?
Tiny bike, of course.
It's not like he's a really big guy.
I mean, it's not like he's a skateboarder or anything.
It's not like you're a big guy with a gen.
I've seen a lot of people with mufflers that are too loud.
BANG BANG BANG BANG!
That Godfurger I mentioned earlier...
Those are the kind of people.
You know, like the horns.
Like, "Ho, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hero.
Godfarjah's that...
TAIGEN WOOLOW.
It doesn't go all the way to the end.
That's why I'm making it.
BAPEPEPEN
Bumpe-pe-pe-pe.
Just the sounds you can pick up?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're the same sex as me...
I'd be like, "I used to hear that at night.
Bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam.
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum
I was so energetic.
I'm fine.
You can ask Mr. Shaw of the silver medium for more details.
Those guys on the stage.
We just saw them from the field
We just saw them from the field and said, "Wow!
All right, then.
Let's hear from them.
This one's good, too.
I showed you a picture of it once.
It depends on where you go in Yokohama.
It depends on where you live.
People who have never lived in Yokohama
I think people who have never lived in Yokohama think it's a flat place.
That's right.
It's a shame if you can't see the harbor.
This is reclaimed land.
Of course, it is flat.
In fact, if you live in Yokohama, you can see that...
Most of Yokohama is like this.
There are mountains and slopes.
Of course, there are flat areas.
That's why...
Fuji can be seen from some places.
Well, now...
I'm sorry if I'm being sarcastic, but...
Mt. Fuji
Fuji can be seen clearly.
Fuji is the highest mountain in Japan.
It's 3,776 meters high.
The second highest mountain.
You said that the other day.
What was it?
It's not Takao-san!
What second Takao?
Famous?
Famous? For kids in Tokyo...
Takao-san...
I'm sure he'll climb the mountain.
I have a short feeling
He's like Takeyama.
Why Takeyama?
It's a bamboo grove in the back.
Bamboo grove?
So So-san?
It's closer.
Kitayama?
Wait a minute... Kita what?
That's not a mountain, it's more like...
It's more like a mountain.
Kitadake.
Why do they call it a mountain?
There's a normal way to read it.
Kitayama?
North is the north of Namboku, right?
You got it wrong on purpose.
Pay.
Mah-jongg.
Pei, yan.
Pay-yan.
Why mah-jongg?
Mr. Shah
May I ask you to step away from mah-jongg?
Kitadake
Kitadake.
I'm number two.
It's in the Southern Alps.
When you see it from Yokohama
you would never be able to see it from Yokohama.
Because there are so many mountains in front of us.
Only Kitadake and its surrounding area
Suddenly, the mountains are low.
You can see it from here.
Just like that.
When the condition is really good
Fuji and Kitadake can both be seen
Fuji and Kitadake at the same time.
It's really nice!
By the way
Yokohama City Aomaku
Don't give me a guide beacon!
You mean you've been hit.
That's how Mr. Seaman feels, isn't it?
I love this scene.
So...
From Yokohama City's blue curtain
From early January
From early January to early March
on a day when there is no haze.
you can see Mt. Kitadake (北岳) in the Southern Alps
of the Southern Alps can be seen over the valley.
Pei-Dake (not Kitadake)
Pei, not Kitadake, can be seen over the valley.
Mt. Pei
It looks like this.
This is only in the north.
This is only the north.
This is what it looks like from the blue curtain.
From my hometown, you can see the mountain and the mountain next to it.
Mt. Fuji is here.
Isn't this a little white?
Could this be it?
This is probably it. It's just a little hidden in the back.
Oh, I see.
Wow!
This is probably because the blue curtain is a lot closer to the mountain than my place.
It's a little bit hidden.
When you get to my place...
I mean, it's not like I own the land, but...
I'm like a landowner.
When you come to me, you can just see it like this.
Oh, I see.
It's nice.
Mountains are nice.
I want to climb a mountain.
By the way...
It's been a while...
Rasha?
Oh, it's been a while.
Ajuni
Bunkyo-ku, Tokyo
Thank you very much.
Aloha everyone!
I am a master land
I don't eat ramen very often
To be precise, I don't go to restaurants to eat ramen.
I only go once a year when someone invites me.
Once a year, and I only go by myself once every five years.
I go by myself once every 5 years or so.
But I went to a ramen restaurant!
I have been going to Ramen for about 15 years now.
I've been an AKB fan for about 15 years now.
I have been an AKB fan for about 15 years.
I've been a fan of AKB for almost 10 years.
Rina Oda
is graduating.
She's known for her love of ramen.
That's right.
This time we went to a ramen shop she recommended!
That's right
Hiyoshi's Ramen Nishida
Hiyoshi is that Hiyoshi?
Is it there?
I got no reply.
Hiyoshi
There is no reply
Hiyoshi's ramen Nishida-san
It says that the broth is made from boiled chicken and dried sardines!
Boiled chicken and dried fish?
That's amazing!
Chicken and...
Odayirina-san is the owner of Kanagawa Prefecture?
I didn't know that.
She did a lot of things for Kanagawa.
I was a one-day warden of Sagamihara Police Department the other day.
Sagamihara Police Department's on Route 20, right?
I remember going there to pick up purses and stuff.
Really?
What was it?
Why did I go there?
Right there, on 16.
Number 16.
It's on the side of the 16.
Yes, sir.
It's big.
Maybe.
No, no, no, no.
Well, well, well, well.
yes yes yes yes
So...
After graduation
Please invite him to Kanagawa Debel.
Let's talk ramen!
Let's talk about ramen together.
I don't think so.
Hey...
I like your ramen.
It's fun.
This is good, right?
If you know what I'm talking about.
I'm gonna get these noodles right.
Hey.
You laid them out so nicely.
It's like this.
They decorated it.
Stylish.
This is...
This is delicious.
Yes, it is.
Carefully made.
Right?
These are dark.
It's very dark.
On the contrary, the green color is...
The green onion.
Aji-tama (seasoned eggs)...
I bet it's delicious.
It's not good.
Thank you very much.
Nice rashers.
If it's in Hiyoshi, I'm already going tomorrow.
Really
Nishida
That's all I have to say
There is one more thing
One more thing
It's Ren-chan's rah-rah!
Everyone is going to ramen
What a surprise!
The winner is from Hokkaido!
Mr. Asahikawa!
That's great!
It's where the North Foxes live.
Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Ta-da!
It's where they say "hokker.
The kids are in the middle of eating.
Let's go play.
Let's make love.
You two don't look anything alike.
We're trying to mimic each other.
But they're not very good.
I don't know what to say.
That's the most annoying part.
That's true.
We're doing it together.
Neither one of us is like the other.
It's bad for the listener.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm just so excited to have ramen in front of me.
18 year old woman
Thank you
Thank you very much.
I've been to Asahikawa once.
It's a great place.
The mountains are just like that.
Not the mountain I just mentioned.
Taisetsuyama.
It's like a famous lump of mountain.
Like Yaesaki.
It's so close.
So close.
It was early summer.
But there was still snow on the ground.
That's right... until early summer.
And all of a sudden, in the city...
There's a big pile of snow...
Like a mountain.
Suddenly...
I looked closer to see what it was.
They shovel snow during the winter.
They dump the snow there.
It's a big mound.
It's amazing.
It's like a hamagura.
Maybe we should wait until it melts.
There's nowhere to dump it.
See that?
I'm from Hokkaido.
Why the sour look?
You don't look like a hometown girl.
That's true.
I don't even know where he's from.
It's ruder than people from Hokkaido.
So...
Master Sapong...
Koma One Devil
I went from Asakagawa to Sapporo the other day on an errand
I went to Sapporo.
I had miso ramen for lunch.
It was so good that I'm sending it to you.
The homemade bamboo shoots were also delicious!
The soup was so rich and thick
My cold body was also chewy!
By the way
Miso ramen has an image of putting butter and corn
But actually, people in Hokkaido don't put much butter and corn in their miso ramen.
but in fact, people in Hokkaido don't put much butter and corn.
Oh, really?
Is that so?
Why?
You don't have to pretend.
You don't have to pretend you're from Hokkaido.
You can't get in?
Can't you come over here and let me in?
I was surprised to see you here.
I'm surprised.
You know what I'm talking about.
I'm a little shocked.
I'm going to make some kind of miso butter corn.
I can see why.
With a special corn-squeeze spoon.
Yes, that's right.
It's an amime.
You eat it like this.
So...
You don't have a special spoon for corn squeegee in Hokkaido?
Is it possible that you don't have it in Hokkaido?
I don't think so.
I don't think so...
But there might not be for sure.
In Hokkaido
I always eat it when I go on an expedition.
It's true that we don't have it.
I see. It's a part of our culture.
That's right.
When miso ramen comes here
It would be delicious if you put it in again when it starts.
That lenghae...
That's why I'm here, Rasia.
Wow!
It's true, miso ramen in Hokkaido is like this
That's what it looks like
Shimamaru!
It's simple.
Very simple!
With bean sprouts.
Hokkaido people say it's good, so it must be pretty good.
Of course it is.
You know something? Like good miso ramen?
But...
It's a fake, so there's no way he knows.
Where are you really from?
Oh, no.
I'm from Hokkaido.
Oh.
Listen.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well.
At least...
Rasia at least.
They don't even put miso or anything on it.
It's common to have kikurage mushrooms on top
Kikurage, green onion, bamboo shoots
Chashu pork
And this one has onion and bean sprouts.
There are bean sprouts on it.
Wow!
I love it!
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
Hey, guys!
If I didn't know any better...
I thought they put it in theirs.
I see.
I'm going to go to...
Suzuki's or something.
You know that place where you see the ramen that tourists come to?
That's why it's there.
Corn...
There was a lot of corn.
They piled it up like this.
I thought, "That's the real Hokkaido.
But the Hokkaido people don't do that.
I see.
Well, well, well.
Well then, let's continue.
If you have any more letters...
If you have any more letters, please send them to us.
I'm looking forward to hearing from you.
So...
And now, to our live audience...
Good evening!
I said Nishiki! Shut up!
I like it. It's like Nishiki, Nishiki, Nishiki.
I'd like to announce something here.
The goods you are looking for, this is Sakoshi
This is Sakoshi, the actual Sakoshi, like this.
It's cute! It's like this!
You can put all kinds of things in here.
It's amazing back here. Side by side...
Wow!
People! You're right.
This is really something, isn't it?
I'm probably the head of the year.
Sawamoto is the homeroom teacher.
And he's like a student.
I see.
It's nice.
Logo and all.
It's pretty versatile.
Transparency.
It can hold a lot of easily identifiable items.
Look at this.
Look.
Oh, wow.
It's a finger holder.
It's got magic.
Look at this.
It's this big.
It can hold everything.
It's gonna hold a lot.
Look at this.
Look.
I don't know.
It's got this. It's got this.
So you can put it on like this?
Like this.
Come on, guys.
I like this one.
Side by side.
It's cute.
Is this...
Goods for sale?
It's limited, isn't it?
Saturday, February 3rd.
It's made-to-order.
Saturday, February 3rd, 23:59.
That means we'll do it until the end of the day on Saturday.
It will end on Sunday.
Sunday, it will end on Sunday.
We hope you all enjoy
Please give us a sakosh
Please come and join us!
Saqoosh.
I'm making my debut in Taikanai.
Tickets for the general public are now on sale.
Tickets are on sale now.
Next!
Yes, it's in a month, five months from now... two months from now, January 31st.
Osaka?
Wow, it's going so fast!
It's really fast.
It really is.
What a surprise!
Is this the real world?
Time is moving a little fast.
It's like a kalarelian world.
I feel like this year is going really fast.
It's early
I don't know, maybe that's why
I haven't had a lot of things to be excited about this year
I'm like, "Oh my God!
So I'm just kind of taking it easy.
I've been taking it easy, and it's already been a year.
This is no good.
Next year will be a year of upheaval!
No, no, no, this year
A year of upheaval.
I'm going to make this a summer to remember!
It's still winter.
We have a little more time.
Yes, sir.
So...
Oh, no, no, no...
It's gone in a blink of an eye even as I'm doing this.
But I'm feeling pretty good right now.
I felt fulfilled.
I said, "I'm going to make this a summer I'll never forget.
I said I'd make it a summer to remember.
Just for saying that.
I'm thinking that every summer will be the only summer I'll remember.
That's true.
I don't really think about it in the winter.
But I do in the summer.
Something dramatic happens in the summer.
I see.
Seasonally, too.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I'd rather live in the summer than the winter.
I'm a person who can live more comfortably in summer than in winter.
I don't like cold weather.
That's why.
But this year, I've decided to be a little more careful with my sunburn.
Last year I had a great
I had a relieve.
I was wearing short sleeves.
And then I got all black.
I'll be careful this year.
I'm not supposed to get sunburned nowadays.
And men, too.
I'm a little concerned about it.
It's like...
They're all going to the tanning salon and tanning themselves.
They said it would make them popular.
"I'm going to be popular.
They went into a capsule and ended up like this.
You were tanning?
Yeah, you know...
I was a little out of sorts back then.
You don't burn things when you're out of sorts.
No, you don't.
Not at all.
You're baked.
I thought I wanted to be popular, but I don't know.
But now it's just that...
Do you prefer it white?
I looked back at the picture and saw black.
I'm trying to be careful.
Last year.
Well, well, well... it wasn't like that.
That said...
I hope you are all looking forward to the big Ribble.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
I'll never completely forget it there again.
Spring
I think it's going to be a spring day.
I look forward to seeing you there.
For the last time.
I've been waiting for you to say a few words.
Let's wrap it up.
Let's do this Nanfaijin today.
Let's do this.
That's great.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's make it an unforgettable spring!
Is it January or is it already the 31st?
Today.
You mean it's actually the 31st?
Well, that's not good.
Time's going by faster than I expected.